Rémi RENARD

45000 Orléans

06-58-40-95-18

remi.renard@coda-student.school Class B license + Car/Motorcycle RQTH - 31 years old

Mobility région Parisienne/ Centre Val-de-Loire/ Télé-travail

Looking for a work-study program starting today.

As a former judoka at the Pôle Espoir, I stand out for my tenacity, focus, and ability to achieve ambitious goals.

SKILLS

EXPERTISE

Develop complete web applications, front & back end

Design and optimize databases

Integrate APIs and external services

Ensure application security and performance

Deploy and maintain projects in production

SOFT SKILLS

Team spirit and effective collaboration.

Ability to adapt to new tools.

IT project manager

Rigorous and detail-oriented.

Perseverance in the face of technical challenges.

Autonomy in project management.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coda and personnal projects

https://remirenard509.github.io/portfolioMaster

https://github.com/remirenard509

https://gitlab.com/rem.renard36

linkedin.com/in/remi-renard-developpeur-full-stack/

Teacher of mathematics and digital and technological sciences

Acadomia from Sept. 2023 to June 2024 (1 year)

Lycée Jacques Monod, Saint Jean de Braye Sept 2019 to June 2020 (1 year)

EDUCATION

Master's in IT Project Management & Green IT september 25

Bachelor's in Full Stack Development, CODA

September 24 (1year)

Master's degree in MEEF, University of Orleans

Sept 2018 to June 2020 (2 years)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Details of my work-study program and more can be found in my portfolio above.

I have traveled to Thailand and India.

I have participated in workshops on digital frescoes and responsible digital technology.

I am in the process of starting a business.